- I'll be over there waiting for you.
- Okay.
Is your name Matthew? I want some action.
Officer...
I swear I'm clean.
I'm just waiting here for a friend.
You gonna bust me for nothing, man?
I'm not a cop.
- I ain't no cop.
- Then why ask me for action?
Because she sent me over.
I suppose that ain't a.38
you got in your sock.
.38? No.
I'm clean, man.
- Shit. You're a real cowboy?
- Yeah.
That's nice.
It's all right.
$15, 15 minutes. $25, half an hour.
Shit.
Cowboy, huh?
I once had a horse in Coney Island.
She got hit by a car.
Take it or leave it.
If you wanna save yourself some money,
don't fuck her.
'Cause you'll be back every night
for more.
She's twelve-and-a-half years old.
You ain't never had no pussy like that.
You can do anything with her...
come on her, fuck her in the mouth,
fuck her in the ass, come on her face.
She'll get your cock so hard,
she'll make it explode.
But no rough stuff. All right?
All right, I'll take it.
Hey, man! Take out no money over here.
You gonna fuck me?
You're gonna fuck her.
You give her the money.
Catch you later, copper.
- What did you say?
- See you later, copper.
I'm no cop, man.
If you are, it's entrapment already.
I'm hip.
Buddy, you don't look hip.
Go ahead, have yourself a good time.
You're a funny guy.
But looks aren't everything.